USS Arizona Collection, 1907-2015 (bulk 1915-1941)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 3: Objects, circa 1911-1983
  This series contains three dimensional objects as well as memorial and commemorative objects. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction. Some of the materials within this series are on permanent exhibit as part of the USS Arizona Exhibit located at the University of Arizona Student Union Memorial Center.
  - United States Flag, First to Fly over Sunken USS Arizona, 50-2-1, 1950 March 07 (Box 42, Item 1)
  - USS Arizona Bell, 51-1-1, 1915 (Box 42, Item 2)
  - USS Arizona Model in Glass and Wooden Case made by Fred Blesy, 18"w x 48"l x 24"h, 55-2-1, circa 1955 (Box 42, Item 3)
  - Copy of New Testament taken from Body of Unidentified Sailor who was Killed during Japanese Attack on Pearl Harbor, 55-3-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 4)
  - Wooden Glass Case with 4 Pieces of Shrapnel Removed from USS Arizona, 55-3-2, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 5)
  - Bronze Plaque Mounted on Wood; "USS Arizona Served in the World War April 6, 1917 to November 11, 1918 Battleship Atlantic Fleet", 57-1-1, undated (Box 42, Item 6)
    Item was retrieved from the USS Arizona, December 10, 1941.
  - Revell Brand USS Arizona Model Mounted on Wooden Plank, 57-2-1, circa 1957 (Box 42, Item 7)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Bed on Ford Island, T.H. Removed 1941 December 07, 58-1-1 (Box 42, Item 8)
  - Military Sword Belt of Daniel J. Condon, 59-1-1, circa 1941 (Box 42, Item 9)
  - Copy of the Holy Bible from USS Arizona, 61-1-1, undated (Box 42, Item 10)
  - Asiatic Campaign Medal (1941-1945) Belonging to J. Horrocks who Lies Entombed on the USS Arizona, 62-2-1 (Box 42, Item 11)
  - Mini Life Saver from USS Arizona, 63-4-1, undated (Box 42, Item 12)
  - Voltage Information Plate from Japanese Two-Man Submarine Sunk in Pearl Harbor, 64-5-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 13)
  - Captain's Pennant from USS Arizona, 67-2-1, 1937 October 26 (Box 42, Item 14)
  - Captain's Streamer from USS Arizona, 67-2-2, 1937 December (Box 42, Item 15)
  - Brass Shield from USS Sperry Mounted on Wood, in Memoriam for USS Arizona, 67-3-1 (Box 42, Item 16)
  - U.S. Navy Gangplank Name Plate, 67-5-1a (Box 42, Item 17)
  - Long Beach Gangplank Name Plate, 67-5-1b (Box 42, Item 18)
  - USS Arizona Gangplank Name Plate, 67-5-1c (Box 42, Item 19)
  - Sailor's Dress Hat from USS Arizona, 68-8-1 (Box 42, Item 20)
  - 1923 Dance Program from Anniversary Ball, 68-2-1abc (Box 42, Item 21)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Pearl Harbor, 70-2-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 22)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Pearl Harbor, 70-2-2, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 23)
  - Piece of Aluminum, Painted, from Japanese Airplane from Pearl Harbor, 70-2-3, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 24)
  - Piece of Aluminum, Painted, from Japanese Airplane from Pearl Harbor, 70-2-4, 1941 December 07 (Box 42, Item 25)
  - Gray Metal Slice Through a 5" Gun Barrel from Secondary Battery or USS Arizona, 74-1-1 (Box 42, Item 26)
  - Champagne Bottle and Rope used to Christen the USS Arizona on June 19, 1915, 74-3-1a,c (Box 42, Item 27)
  - Medal Worn by Ester Ross at USS Arizona Christening Ceremony, June 19, 1915, 74-3-2 (Box 42, Item 28)
  - 50 Caliber Machine Gun Cases Salvaged from USS Arizona, 76-2-1-2 (Box 42, Item 29)
  - Salvaged Halyard Snaps from USS Arizona Flag Staff, 76-2-3-4 (Box 42, Item 30)
  - Machine Gun Projectile, Possibly Japanese, Salvaged from Pearl Harbor, 76-2-5 (Box 42, Item 32)
  - Machine Gun Projectile, Possibly Japanese, Salvaged from Pearl Harbor, 76-2-5 (Box 42, Item 33)
  - 10’x15’ United States Flag which was Flown over the U.S. capitol, April 20, 1976, 76-5-1 (Box 42, Item 34)
  - Wood plank from Quarterdeck of USS Arizona, 77-1-1, 1934 (Box 42, Item 35)
  - Lamp with Plaster Base of Cliff and Light Tower, 77-1-6ab (Box 42, Item 36)
  - Leather Bound Log and USS Arizona Scrapbook (empty), 77-3-6 (Box 42, Item 33)
  - Expended Shell Casings (3), 77-3-8, 9, 10 (Box 42, Item 34)
  - Plaque Framed with two Artillery Shells, 77-3-11ab, undated (Box 42, Item 35)
  - Single Bulb Lamps Made from Various Caliber Rifle Shells and Stainless Steel, Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona 1931-1938" on Base, 77-3-12, 13 (Box 42, Item 36)
  - Ash Trays Made from Various Caliber Rifle Shells Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona, 1931-1938, 77-3-14, 15ab (Box 42, Item 37)
  - Practice Bomb Casings Inscribed "USS Arizona, Turret One, 1931-1938, 77-3-16, 17 (Box 42, Item 38)
  - Leather Bound Log and Photo Album, "Log Album 1931" Inscribed on Front, 77-3-35 (Box 42, Item 39)
  - Black Neck Cloth Tied Around Neck Opening of Dress White Jumper. "Watkins" in Hand-Stitched on Center Fold, 77-3-36 (Box 42, Item 40)
  - Chief Petty Officer’s Uniform, Jacket and Pants Donated by Warren C. Kaiser, 79-1-1ab, circa 1936-1940 (Box 42, Item 41)
  - U.S. Navy Uniform Worn in Time of Peace, 79-1-2, circa 1936-1940 (Box 42, Item 42)
  - USS Arizona Football Sweater, Donated by Alvin Alison Talbot who served on the USS Arizona from 1928-1934, 79-3-1 (Box 42, Item 43)
  - Spyglass Retrieved from the USS Arizona, December 15-19, 1945, 81-2-1ab (Box 42, Item 44)
  - Lamp with Plaster Cast, 80-1-1, undated (Box 42, Item 45)
  - Pair of Handmade Candlesticks of Lignum Vitae and Teak, 77-1-7ab, circa 1927-1934 (Box 42, Item 46)
  - Piece of Turret 3 from USS Arizona Embedded in Hexagonally Shaped Piece of Plastic, 83-2-6 (Box 42, Item 47)
  - USS Arizona Boarding Book, 84-3-1, 1916 (Box 42, Item 48)
  - Hand Colored Photo Blowup of the USS Arizona at Sea, 1935; Bronze Plaque Accompanying Photo with Inscription "U.S.S. Arizona, New York Navy Yard June 19, 1915, Pearl Harbor, December 7, 1941 84-6-1, 2 (Box 42, Item 49)
  - Two Slices from 6" Anti-Aircraft Guns which were Firing when USS Arizona was Sunk, December 7, 1941, 84-7-1, 2 (Box 42, Item 50)
  - Log Book Photograph Album, Leather Bound (empty), 84-19-11 (Box 42, Item 51)
  - Steel Ring Wheel of Japanese Bomber Shot Down by USS Honolulu, 84-24-1 (Box 42, Item 52)
  - 5" Anti Aircraft Shrapnel, Time Fuse from Husband on USS Arizona, 84-24-2 (Box 42, Item 53)
  - #1400 Armor Piercing Projectile-Tungsten, Nickel and Steel, Probably Japanese, December 7, 1941, 84-24-3 (Box 42, Item 54)
  - Piece of Torpedo Plane Shot Down By USS Curtis, December 7, 1941, 84-24-4 (Box 42, Item 55)
  - Piece of Quarterdeck, Teak, USS Arizona, December 7, 1941, 84-24-5 (Box 42, Item 55)
  - White Plastic Sign with Black Lettering, reads "USS Arizona", 84-24-6 (Box 42, Item 55)
  - USS Arizona ID Tags Donated by Warren Kaiser, 84-24-7, 8,9,10, undated (Box 42, Item 55)
  - Souvenir Medal USS Arizona 1925, 84-24-11, undated (Box 42, Item 56)
  - United States Flag Taken off an Unidentified Body On board USS Arizona, December 7, 1941, 84-24-13 (Box 42, Item 56)
  - USS Arizona Model by Chris Cowheard, 87-5-1, undated (Box 42, Item 57)
  - United States Navy Uniform, undated (Box 43, Item 1)
  - Christmas Tablecloth, 67-6-1, 1939 (Box 43, Item 2)
  - USS Arizona Purple Felt Banner, 77-3-18, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43, Item 3)
  - USS Arizona Silk Pillow Case with Mother of Mine Poem, 85-9-2, circa 1936-1939 (Box 43, Item 4)
  - United States Flag, 76-5-1, undated (Box 43, Item 5)
  - United States Flag, Donated by William Osborne to be raised over State Capitol Buildings, the USS Arizona Memorial, and the University of Arizona on December 7 of each Year, 85-10-1 (Box 43, Item 6)
  - Metal Plaque with USS Arizona New York Navy Yard, June 19, 1915 Pearl Harbor, December 7, 1941 Inscription, 84-6-2 (Box 43, Item 7)
  - USS North Carolina Pennant, 77-3-19, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43, Item 8)
  - United States Navy Eagle Lock, circa 1911 (Box 43, Item 9)
  - Water Bottle Used to Christen USS Arizona on June 19, 1915, 74-3-1b (Box 43 A, Item 1)
  - 50 Caliber Machine Gun Casing Salvaged from Attack on Pearl Harbor, 76-2-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 B, Item 1)
  - 50 Caliber Machine Gun Casing Salvaged from Attack on Pearl Harbor, 76-2-2, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 B, Item 2)
  - Halyard Snaps from USS Arizona Flagstaff Salvaged from Attack on Pearl Harbor, 76-2-3, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 B, Item 3)
  - Halyard Snaps from USS Arizona Flagstaff Salvaged from Attack on Pearl Harbor, 76-2-4, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 B, Item 4)
  - Machine Gun Projectile Salvaged from Attack on Pearl Harbor, 76-2-4, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 B, Item 5)
  - Handmade Pair of Candlesticks of Lignum Vitae and Teak, 77-1-7ab, circa 1927-1934 (Box 43 C, Item 1)
  - Polished Expended Shell Casing with Initials WAW-45-CL-RV Scribed and Stamped on Base, 77-3-8, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 D, Item 1)
  - Polished Expended Shell Casing with Stamped Marking 40mm-MK3, C1-RV Outer Casing Scribed with Female Figure and "Sugar Tit", 77-3-9, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 D, Item 2)
  - Polished Expended Shell Casing with Stamped Marking 40mm-MK3, 45-C1-RV Outer Casing Scribed with Female Figure and Heart with "Susie Gal", 77-3-10, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 D, Item 3)
  - Photograph of William A. Watkins and Donald Barley in Handmade Photograph Stand Made from Various Rifle and Pistol Shells and Stainless Steel, 77-3-11abc, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 E, Item 1)
  - Lighter Made from Expended Small Caliber Shell Casing, 77-3-34abc, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 E, Item 2)
  - Single Bulb Lamp Made from Various Caliber Rifle Shells and Stainless Steel Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona, 1931-1938, 77-3-12, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 F, Item 1)
  - Single Bulb Lamp Made from Various Caliber Rifle Shells and Stainless Steel Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona, 1931-1938, 77-3-13, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 F, Item 2)
  - Practice Bomb Casing Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona, 1931-1938, 77-3-16, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 G, Item 1)
  - Practice Bomb Casing Inscribed "Watkins, Turret One, USS Arizona, 1931-1938, Code 227620 (A)1, 77-3-17, circa 1931-1938 (Box 43 G, Item 2)
  - Steel Ring Wheel of Japanese Bomber Shot Down by USS Honolulu, 84-24-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 H, Item 1)
  - 5" Anti-Aircraft Shrapnel Time Fuse from Husband, 84-24-2, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 H, Item 2)
  - #1400 Armor Piercing Projectile-Tungsten, Nickel and Steel, 84-24-3, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 H, Item 3)
  - Piece of Japanese Torpedo Plane Shot Down by USS Curtis, 84-24-4, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 H, Item 4)
  - Tied USS Arizona ID Tags, A301, A309, A108, A313, 84-24-7-10 (Box 43 H, Item 5)
  - Piece of Shrapnel, American, 84-24-15, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 H, Item 6)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Bed on Ford Island, T.H., 58-1-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 I, Item 1)
  - Voltage Information Plate from Japanese Two-Man Submarine Sunk in Pearl Harbor, 64-5-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 I, Item 2)
  - 1923 Dance Program from Anniversary Ball; Consists of Small Medal and Two Paper Dance Lists on Small Ring with Cord Attached, 68-2-1 (Box 43 I, Item 3)
  - Metal Name Tag with Blue Ribbon and Medal with 1924 E, 71-3-4b (Box 43 I, Item 4)
  - Piece of Turret 3 Taken from USS Arizona on 20th Anniversary of Pearl Harbor Attack Embedded in Hexagon Shaped Piece of Plastic, 83-2-6, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 I, Item 5)
  - US Navy Pen, Pencil, and Case Set, 84-32-1abc, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 I, Item 5)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Pearl Harbor Attack, 70-2-1, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 J, Item 1)
  - Piece of Shrapnel from Pearl Harbor Attack, 70-2-2, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 J, Item 2)
  - Pained Piece from Japanese Airplane Shot Down During Pearl Harbor Attack, 70-2-3, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 J, Item 3)
  - Pained Piece from Japanese Airplane Shot Down During Pearl Harbor Attack, 70-2-4, 1941 December 07 (Box 43 J, Item 3)
  - American Heritage China Battleship USS Arizona Last Cruise Commemorative Plate with stand from Original Painting by Edward Ries, 83-1-1, 1983 (Box 44, Item 1)
  - USS Arizona Matchbook, 84-24-12, undated (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Asiatic Pacific Campaign Medallion, 1941-1-45, 84-24-11 (Box 44, Item 3)
  - USS Arizona Historian Light, undated (Box 45, Item 1)
- Series 4: Audio Visual Materials, 1981-1984
  This series contains audio visual materials and is comprised of cassette tapes of oral histories of sailors who served on the USS Arizona as well as VHS tapes of USS Arizona memorial ceremonies. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
  - 40th Anniversary & Convention Reunion: Pearl Harbor Sunset Service, Cassette Tape, 84-30-3, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Charles Jackson Experiences on December 7, 1941, Cassette Tape, 84-30-2, 1984 March 2 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Charles Jackson Experiences on December 7, 1941,, CD MASTER, RESTRICTED, 1984 March 2 (Box 46, Folder 2a)
  - Joe Potenza Recollections of Life on the USS Arizona, Cassette Tape, 84-31-3, 1984 June 21 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Joe Potenza Recollections of Life on the USS Arizona, CD MASTER, RESTRICTED, 1984 June 21 (Box 46, Folder 3a)
  - Martin Kos, Cassette Tape, 84-40-1, 1984 December 19 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Martin Kos, CD MASTER, RESTRICTED, 1984 December 19 (Box 46, Folder 4a)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Bell Peal copy of Original recording made by G. Harner, Cassette Tape, 84-13-1, 1984 April (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Bell Peal copy of Original recording made by G. Harner, CD MASTER RESTRICTED, 1984 April (Box 46, Folder 5a)
  - USS Arizona Memorial Ceremony, VHS Cassette, 85-2-1, 1984 December 9 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Series 5: USS Arizona Reunion Association, Crew-Kin and Related Materials, 1960-2007
  This series has seven subseries and consists of materials created by the USS Arizona Reunion Association and USS Arizona Crew-Kin Association, an association comprised of individuals who served on the USS Arizona and their kin.
  - Subseries 1: Documents, 1960-2007
    This subseries contains documents including ship rosters, and books and other printed materials related to the history of the USS Arizona and the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, Hawaii. Box 49, folder 5 contains a recounting of December 7, 1941 attack on Pearl Harbor by William D. Osborne Jr.
    - USS Arizona Memorial Foundation General Information, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association General Information, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association and Crew-Kin Bylaws, 1979-2000 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Financial Information, 1984-1995 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Stationary, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Crew-Kin Rosters, 1978-1987 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Deceased Members Rosters, circa 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Rosters, 1980 – 2000 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Membership Roster, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Membership Roster, 1995 – 1996 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association and Crew-Kin Reunion Attendees, 1979 – 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Reunion Itineraries, 1981 – 2001 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Historian Reports, 1989 – 1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Museum Association Newsletter, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Crew-Kin Newsletters, 1982 – 1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Newsletters, 1978 – 1983 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Newsletters, 1984-1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Newsletters, 1992-1997 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      Folder contains the 1992 and 1994 edition of the USS Arizona Reunion Association newsletters The Arizonian.
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Newsletters, 1998-2007 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - 50th Anniversary Reunion Yearbook Advance Sales, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - USS Arizona Crew Members Obituaries, 1973 – 2006 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - USS Arizona Enlisted Men Rosters, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - General Information about the USS Arizona and Pearl Harbor Attack, 1941-2005 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Brochures and Pamphlets, 1991 – 2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Folder contains the 50th, 60th, and 65th anniversary of the Pearl Harbor attack materials and the USS Arizona Memorial flagpole dedication materials.
    - USS Arizona Memorial Souvenirs, 1984-2005 (1 of 2), undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - USS Arizona Memorial Souvenirs, 1984-2005 (2 of 2), undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Folder contains the USS Arizona Memorial calendar.
    - Books Relating to the USS Arizona Collection (Box 50, Folder 1)
      And I Was There – Pearl Harbor and Midway – Breaking the Secrets
      Arizona’s Heart Beats
      Battleship Arizona: An Illustrated History
      Battleship Country: The Battle Fleet at San Pedro – Long Beach, California
      Dec. 7 1941: The Day the Japanese Attacked Pearl Harbor
      East Wind Rain: A Pictorial History of the Pearl Harbor Attack
      On Guard in Paradise
      Pearl Harbor and the USS Arizona Memorial: A Pictorial History
      Remembering Pearl Harbor: The Story of the USS Arizona Memorial
      Slow Dance to Pearl Harbor: A Tin Can Ensign in Prewar America
      USS Arizona’s Last Band: The History of U.S. Navy Band Number 22
      USS Arizona Memorial: Pearl Harbor Navy Yard
      World War II: A Visual Encyclopedia
      You Can’t Go Incognito in a Battleship
    - Magazine Articles Relating to the USS Arizona, 1966-1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Magazine Articles Relating to the USS Arizona, 1991-2004 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper Articles Relating to the USS Arizona (1 of 2), 1948-2011 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Newspaper Articles Relating to the USS Arizona (2 of 2), 1948-2011 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.44, 70-88, 1978, 1982-1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.89-96, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.97-105, 1989-1991 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.106-114, 1991-1993 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.115-123, 1993-1995 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.124-133, 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Pearl Harbor Gram, no.134, 136, 148-149, 153-157, 1998-2004 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - World War II Presents Pearl Harbor Commemorative Issue, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - United States Naval Institute Proceedings, Vol. 103/12/898, 1977 December (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - After the Battle, Pearl Harbor Then and Now, no.38, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Battleships in Action, Vol.3, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - American Heritage, Vol. 42, no. 8, 1991 December (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - American History Illustrated, Vol. 16, no.5, 1991 November / December (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Life Magazine, Pearl Harbor, December 4, 1941 – December 7, 1991, 1991 Fall (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Naval History, Vol. 5, no. 4, 1991 Winter (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Naval History, Vol. 9, no. 3, 1995 May, June (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings, 1991 December (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - World War II Chronicles, Vol.1, no.1, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Life Magazine, Our Finest Hour: Voices of the World War II Generation, 2000 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 2: Photographs, 1919-2002
    This subseries contains photographic materials created by Cline E. Herrin, Roy Hubert, and Joe Vivirito who served as crew members aboard the USS Arizona. These materials document interior and exterior views of the ship, its armament and machinery, crew and personnel engaging in daily activities and duties, US Navy ships, and the Neptune's Court Ceremony. The subseries also contains USS Arizona Reunion Association reunion and ceremony materials. Item titles contain a three digit accession number assigned by the University of Arizona Student Union upon donation of the item. This number consists of a tripartite system that consists of three parts that refer to the year of the item’s acquisition, the transaction number of that year, and the individual specimen number within that transaction.
    - Miscellaneous USS Arizona Photographs, 1919-1941, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
      Folder contains materials that document exterior views of the ship, aircraft, the USS Arizona Memorial in Pearl Harbor, HI, and sailors. Folder also contains a photograph of the USS Arizona at sea in Smyrna, Turkey in 1919.
    - Cline E. Herrin Photographs, 1939, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
      Folder contains materials that document the Neptunus Rex Ceremony, the ship docked at Bremerton, Washington, interior and exterior views of the ship, its armament, 1937 observation aircraft crash, the ship's crew, ship competitions, and the 1939 USS Arizona Rifle Team.
    - Roy Hubert Photographs, 1931-1934 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      Folder contains materials that document the ship at the San Francisco Bay Bridge, the 1931 crew, The USS Arizona in the Norfolk, Virginia Bay, 1931, The 1931 USS Arizona Football Team, the 1933-1934 USS Arizona Basketball Team, and the 1932 Champion Boat Crew.
    - Joe Vivirito Photographs, 1936-1940 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      Folder contains materials that document wrecked aircraft, exterior views of the ship, crew, armament, the Neptunus Rex Ceremony, US Navy Battleships, and The USS Arizona Docked at Long Beach California, 1938.
    - Copies of Jim Vlach Photographs, 1941-1943, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      Folder contains photocopies of photographs from Jim Vlach's photo album. Materials depict Jim Vlach posing with friends and family and date 1942-1943. Folder also contains photocopies of photographs of Jim Vlach's 1996 visit to the USS Arizona Memorial.
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Reunion Photographs, 1941-1943, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association at USS Arizona Memorial, 1989-2001 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      Folder contains images of the 50th and 60th anniversary of the attack on Pearl Harbor celebrations.
    - USS Arizona Memorial Flagpole Dedication Ceremony, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - USS Arizona Reunion Association Scrapbook Pages, 1941, 1986, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Subseries 3: Oral History Transcriptions, 1981-2001
    This subseries is arranged chronologically and contains transcriptions of oral histories conducted with men who served on the USS Arizona during the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor, Hawaii, December 7, 1941.
    - USS Arizona Survivors Oral History Transcriptions, 1981 – 1986 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      Folder contains interviews with John Anderson, James Leamon Forbis, Henry Donald Davidson, Jim Green.
    - USS Arizona Survivors Oral History Transcriptions, 1991-1996 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      Folder contains interviews with Charles William "Bill" Guerin, Larry Elliott, Jim Dick Miller, Glenn Harvey Lane, Russell Lott.
    - USS Arizona Survivors Oral History Transcriptions, 1996 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      Folder contains interviews with Russell McCurdy, Clinton Howard Westbrook, Clyde Jefferson Combs, John Willard Evans, John David Harris.
    - USS Arizona Survivors Oral History Transcriptions, 1996-2001 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      Folder contains interviews with Joseph Kopcho Langdell, Jim Vlach, John Harry Jack McCarron, Everett Owen Reid and Barbara Ellen Goodwin Reid, Edward Louis Wentzlaff.
  - Subseries 4: Correspondence, 1984-2006